(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
SOLD OUT ON YOU
I wanted to introduce the essence in the best possible way,
so I think we'll need a bit more time.
-We'll have it perfectly ready for you. -She must be crazy.
So please think of today as a session to get to know
L'Étoile's La Fin Essence a little bit more.
TO STUDIO C
Please ask any questions you may have through the live chat.
Everyone, let me remind you once more that we will not be selling the product
on tonight's broadcast.
Put down your phones for a moment, and please listen to my explanation.
What surprised me the most as I learned about La Fin Essence
was the raw material that makes up more than 90% of it.
This white flower noori mushroom
is a species native only to Korea,
and it is cultivated exclusively in Deokpung Village.
Even a slight change in temperature or humidity can make them spoil.
Did she just blow a prime-time slot worth millions per minute?
So they're very delicate and require meticulous care.
To be honest, L'Étoile's La Fin Essence
is such a well-known product that needs no introduction from me.
We're getting a lot of questions about not being able to order.
Again, please note that we will not be selling the product
on tonight's broadcast.
Stop the broadcast now and switch to a prerecorded segment!
We'd like to thank you
for taking the time to listen to our introduction
of L'Étoile's La Fin Essence.
We'll be back with the next broadcast as soon as possible.
This has been Dam Ye-jin.
HIT HOMESHOPPING
Dam Ye-jin, you rotten brat.
Have you lost your mind?
Are you taking responsibility?
How can you call yourself a home shopping host?
A home shopping host does not spend a moment on air
on anything else besides selling the product.
You went on TV without knowing that basic rule?
If it's a product that I can't trust 100%,
I can't sell it to customers, Ms. Dong.
Aren't you using them as an excuse?
Get out.
You don't have the right to stand here.
I can't believe her.
That little…
This is ridiculous.
Ms. Dam.
You did a good job.
Ms. Dam,
you were really impressive tonight.
Why did you come to HIT?
You didn't even know how I'd react.
Finding you was all I could think about.
I was sure we'd be on the same page.
You're saying…
that you trusted me, right?
Everyone will eventually realize
that you made the right choice.
But how did you know about this place?
I come here sometimes when I need some fresh air.
I mentioned this place during a recent live I did.
Did you watch it?
No.
I was just joking.
I guess I'm saying nonsense because I can't think straight.
Are you all right?
Thank you for tonight.
In return, I promise to have your back too one day.
You can count on me.
-Mr. Seo. -Did you know about this?
Sir? What do you mean?
MICROBIAL TESTING AND EXPECTED RESULTS
These numbers are much lower than the limit.
This is within the normal range.
Normal? When the growth rate is that high?
Are you sure there were no issues during production?
Mr. Seo, there are microorganisms floating around the air around us.
The point is not to exceed the limit, and as you know,
our essence contains preservatives to prevent that.
It passed even the strict EU standards
without any issues.
You know that better than anyone.
For now, suspend all production this minute.
Hello?
Eric!
What happened to the launch broadcast?
And that showcase? What on earth was that?
I'm asking you what happened!
I'm looking into it.
"Looking into it"?
So you're saying that host did this without even discussing it with you?
I see.
Michelle, don't touch her.
-What? -Don't lay a hand
on Dam Ye-jin.
SOMETHING'S UP IF IT WAS SUDDENLY PULLED DOES THE ESSENCE HAVE PROBLEMS? TELL US!
AS ALWAYS, PASS ON COSMETICS SOLD BY DAM YE-JIN
HIT HOMESHOPPING
How will the broadcast proceed now?
You mean the follow-up broadcast?
Right, yes…
We should get it ready quickly!
With the original contract terms,
we'll schedule it for two consecutive days.
We'll adjust the commission fee as well.
The commission fee too?
Of course, sir.
It was the result of a mistake on our end.
Geez, that Dam Ye-jin.
That oddball was already seen as a liability,
and she ended up causing a huge mess.
Once again, we sincerely apologize.
-In the follow-up broadcast-- -Before that,
we'd like to run another product test.
Would that be all right?
For what?
Dam Ye-jin was called an oddball
because she's different from the other hosts who simply memorize
and recite what our clients want them to say.
What if we rush the broadcast
and something truly goes wrong?
All right, then.
I would like to check as well.
Look at this.
These fools at L'Étoile must have decided to just deny everything for now.
It seems Dam Ye-jin's going to end up taking all the blame.
L'Étoile has issued a statement today
on their official website regarding quality concerns
of their product from a launch broadcast that are spreading across social media.
According to the statement, the broadcast was switched to a showcase
based solely on the host's decision,
and it claims there were no functional issues with the product.
This has sparked a flood of criticism that the broadcast's host, Dam Ye-jin,
may have intervened excessively.
Past partner companies have been stepping forward
with similar allegations.
She checked our samples ten times.
But then, she nitpicked something trivial
and eventually rejected our product.
We even gave up a department store launch because she'd said she would sell them.
That's ridiculous…
MY DEAR DAUGHTER
The person you are calling is unavailable…
MYEONG-HWA
DAM YE-JIN
Mr. Park.
What brings you here at this hour?
I'm sorry to bother you so late.
Could I borrow your phone?
My phone?
Why? Is yours broken?
If it was, I guess you couldn't have called me.
WE'D LIKE TO REQUEST AN INTERVIEW
I TRUSTED YOU AND BOUGHT SO MANY PRODUCTS
TYPICAL ONLINE SELLER
MR. MECHOORI
Hello?
Mr. Mechoori?
Yes.
Has it exceeded the CFU limit?
No, not yet.
Then, why did you call me?
Wear your socks to bed.
What?
I mean…
I read a study somewhere
that wearing socks to bed dilates peripheral blood vessels,
helping with temperature regulation
and better sleep.
Did you call me at this hour to tell me that?
No, it's not that…
I know why you called.
What?
You suddenly called me and started rambling.
You're drunk, right?
No.
-I didn't drink-- -I'm joking.
I'm sure you have a lot on your mind too.
It's late.
You should go and sleep.
Okay.
L'Étoile's headquarters
distanced themselves from Dam Ye-jin and said she acted on her own.
Do you see it the same way?
We're still looking into the matter,
but we can't conclude it was L'Étoile's fault yet.
The numbers from today were still less than half the limit.
Weren't you being too rash?
The decision that day and this discussion today.
Right now, Dam Ye-jin is--
Ms. Dam…
will do a follow-up broadcast
with L'Étoile.
Do you think Ms. Dam
will be all right until then?
HIT WE SELL VALUE WITH SINCERITY
I made the judgment that our trust with customers came before sales.
Even if I were to go back to before the broadcast,
I would make the same choice.
I'll take responsibility for all the consequences of my decision.
"Responsibility"?
How will you take responsibility?
This L'Étoile launch
had 1.5 billion won in sales and a 100 million-won clause riding on it.
Could you handle that?
Do you know that HIT's website
has been flooded with posts from people saying they'll file official complaints
for consumer deception?
Our customers had eagerly awaited the launch.
How will you make up for breaking their trust?
Given the microbial growth rate, it was bound to become an issue.
Power tripping.
Canceling a broadcast by nitpicking a perfectly normal product
is what we call power tripping.
It's because of you!
You made it seem like we abused our power, and HIT's in this huge mess now!
You ran your mouth without even knowing anything.
Director Dong Hyun-ki,
there's no need to hear anything more.
Ms. Dam Ye-jin.
Due to a breach of our contract terms,
effective today,
HIT will be terminating its contract with you.
"We sell value with sincerity."
I…
made the choice to keep the promise that HIT made.
You'll soon realize that my choice…
wasn't wrong.
That little…
-What is she so proud of? -What did she say?
The nerve of her!
-Are you going to let this slide? -She's so smug.
How can she be so shameless?
-I'll carry it-- -It's fine.
You're really going to leave like this?
Holding out here won't get me any shows.
Ms. Dam, why don't you just go and speak to Ms. Dong…
Come on, what's with you? This isn't the end.
I'm Dam Ye-jin, you know.
This is just a tactical retreat for now. I'll be back soon.
So get back to work. Don't slack off because of my absence.
We'll call you.
You better pick up.
Don't try my patience!
Geez, I should block the both of you.
Are you really going to just take the meds again?
Ms. Dam.
What are you going to do if this leads to sleepwalking?
It may seem like nothing is helping at the moment,
but one by one, if you try to resolve--
I…
I'm completely fine,
Doctor.
Isn't that just what you want to believe?
Let's talk inside.
MAKE SURE TO TAKE PROBIOTICS AND DON'T SKIP MEALS
STIR-FRIED SQUID, BRAISED TOFU DOENJANG STEW
You really are a great actress.
People might think you're actually my mom.
Stop being so grumpy.
I'm not here to talk about that.
You must have rushed over in excitement after hearing I got fired.
Show's over now, so leave.
Can't you even manage your health properly?
Just get to the point.
Don't even set foot near the cosmetics industry again.
That's what I came to say.
You came all the way here
just to say that?
You should've stopped when I told you to.
Look!
You couldn't even handle it--
And ran away?
Running away
is what you did when you abandoned your young child,
Ms. Song Myeong-hwa.
MICROBIAL TEST RESULTS
How do the numbers look?
You look so pale.
Are you okay? Is something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
I, Kang Mu-won, can no longer allow this.
Let's go, baby.
-Mu-won. -Yeah?
I'm busy.
Me too. But this will only take a moment.
Come on. Geez.
Hey, Hae-seok.
Can't you just tell me now?
Why are you so obsessed with the numbers?
It's because this is the only way
I can help Ms. Dam.
Is this…
because of what happened back then?
I told you a million times to put that in the past.
It was all because of Choi Woo-su.
He deliberately planned all that, and you were just the victim.
-You didn't have a choice-- -Mu-won!
Let's not talk about that.
We're almost sold out. About 400 orders have come in all at once,
and all the customer service agents are busy.
The queue is full.
Seriously. Thank you all so much.
My goodness.
People who know this product well
are busy stockpiling them.
This lipstick is the top product in Europe, and it went viral in Paris.
Ta-da! Everyone knows this lipstick.
You know,
I had such a really hard time getting enough stock for all of you.
You can buy these
only tonight on The Ji Yun-ji Show.
You have no idea how lucky you are.
Viewer 8739 says, "Yun-ji, can you show us the Modern Red color?"
I was just about to show you this one.
It's cute, right?
The color payoff is excellent, and it applies so smoothly.
DAM YE-JIN
Mom.
Ms. Dam, where are you?
Ms. Dam, can you hear me?
I'm…
-on my way to do the broadcast. -Ms. Dam…
Sir, could you take me to HIT Homeshopping?
Please hurry.
Ms. Dam.
Ms. Dam!
Mom…
Ms. Dam! Where are you right now?
Ms. Dam!
Mom.
I'm…
not going to run away.
SONG MYEONG-HWA COMPACT ONLY AT HIT HOMESHOPPING
Ms. Dam!
Ms. Dam, can you hear me?
Ms. Dam, are you okay?
Let's go.
Mechoori…
Mr. Mechoori.
This is a secret.
She's my mom.
My mom.
Ms. Dam, let's--
I have to go and do the broadcast.
I prepared so hard for this.
Let's go.
MUST TAKE ONLY ONE PACK PER DAY
It's cute, right?
I'm completely fine, Doctor.
Isn't that just what you want to believe?
Sit down. We need to talk.
I'm not feeling well, so I need to rest.
You need to hear this.
Next time.
You don't remember
anything from last night?
Didn't you hear me? I want to rest.
Did you take…
Did you take those pills all at once?
What does it matter to you?
Ms. Dam!
I told you to just leave!
Do you really need to tell me that I've hit rock bottom?
I already know. You don't have to tell me.
I know I'm a complete mess!
But all I can do right now is to pretend that I'm okay!
Why won't you let me even do that?
What…
What if this really is the end for me?
What do I do?
DAM YE-JIN
Hello?
HIT is asking us to send the QA documents again. What's going on?
They should be paying us a penalty fee, but they want a re-inspection?
We've already agreed to do a follow-up broadcast with HIT.
Eric!
Are you out of your mind?
I guess I must be far from home.
Ever since I got here, I've really felt the distance between us.
-Don't change the subject. -Michelle.
-Are you feeling anxious? -What?
You were always kind and generous to me.
But whenever you'd suddenly shout at me like this,
I would think,
"I'm just a piece of gum she's chewing."
A piece of gum you chew on to relieve your stress…
when you're nervous.
But I still wanted to be someone that you needed.
So…
don't spit me out so rashly.
I don't want to stick to the bottom of your soles and cause you trouble.
Do you regret stopping the broadcast that day?
No.
Then, you should be doing well.
Why are you such a mess?
Pack your stuff and come out.
Can't you just leave me be?
Come with me. Please.
Where are we going?
Hey, there!
Come on in. Take a seat.
Right!
I stir-fried sweet potato stems for you, but I forgot.
Stay here, ma'am.
I'll go get them.
She looks so gaunt now.
What else should I feed her?
What does sweetie like?
I don't know either.
Geez. You have the looks but nothing else.
What was that?
Ms. Dam!
Sweetie!
What's wrong? Is she badly ill?
She's malnourished
and very dehydrated.
It seems she's been really worn out.
She even has insomnia,
so her body's pressed on the brakes
because it wants some rest.
Then, will she be okay if she gets enough rest?
Yes, with plenty of rest.
Gosh, what a relief.
I'm so relieved.
At least it wasn't anything worse.
WOORI DEOKPUNG MEDICAL CLINIC
She's awake.
-She's awake! -She's awake!
She's awake!
She's up!
My goodness!
Are you all right?
Yes.
I…
Jung-muk!
Ms. Dam is awake!
Should she go to a big hospital?
Is it serious? What do we do?
She needs rest.
Come here.
How are you feeling?
What's wrong?
I'm hungry.
Goodness!
You should eat then.
It's about that time when you get hungry.
-Yeah? -We should have a feast.
It is about that time. Right?
You understand, right?
-Yes, ma'am. -Yes, ma'am.
Let's do it right.
-Yes, ma'am. -Yes, ma'am. Don't worry.
Ma'am, let me make dinner for you this evening.
Oh, dear.
I totally forgot that my youngest daughter and her husband are visiting tonight.
-Goodness. -Really?
That's too bad.
Our daughter's old room--
It's gone. It's all broken down.
Then, by any chance…
Our house is a huge mess.
Gosh, don't say it like that.
We have a lot of rescue dogs at home.
-Right. -Woof, woof.
Then, what should I do?
Since this is the countryside, there aren't any lodgings here.
Is that the only place left?
-Oh, right. -Right?
-Yeah. -Yeah.
-That's right. -Where?
For goodness' sake.
You still haven't caught on?
This is all a setup.
What?
The choice had already been made for you.
-Ms. Dam. -Yes?
I only brought you to my home
to take responsibility for being partly the cause of your current condition.
So while you're here, please do things my way.
What exactly is "your way"?
You'll find out soon enough.
Let's head inside.
Okay.
-Watch your step. -Right.
Okay, I'll go and unpack first.
I just realized you don't have any spare rooms.
Then, how…
That room! I'll stay there.
That's the bathroom.
I see. It's the bathroom.
Then, where…
That's a room, right? I'll go stay there.
Gosh, it's nice and spacious.
Ms. Dam.
Yes?
Please come here.
Okay.
Can you come over here?
To… To the bed?
It's okay. I can rest in that room.
What? Why?
I'm sure you're sleepy by now.
But there's no bed in there.
It'll be uncomfortable sleeping on the floor,
and you won't be able to sleep.
So just sleep here.
No, it's fine. I'll only be staying for a little while.
You can use the bed.
It's no big deal.
By the way, I just realized there's no TV here either.
I don't have a TV.
-How can you not have a TV? -I hate things that are loud.
You can just lower the volume then.
So do you always live like you're in some kind of retreat?
Don't you get bored?
Aren't you going to eat?
I am eating.
-So you don't use your phone often either? -I don't.
I see.
I guess there are some positives of being unemployed.
I get to take walks in a place like this with nice scenery and fresh air.
I feel much better now.
By the way, where did you see me last night?
I was passing by and spotted you by chance around HIT.
HIT?
But I didn't say anything weird, did I?
No.
I guess I'm getting punished.
The first thing I did when I became a main host
was cut down on sleep.
"Just ten more minutes."
I'd say, "Let's practice for just ten more minutes."
I thought that once I settled down and got used to the job,
I'd be able to sleep well like before.
But I ignored the fact
that the body falls into a routine.
It seems my body is pretty upset with me.
But I don't know how to make it feel better.
You've already achieved a lot by realizing that.
How would you know that?
I once used to be unable to sleep without meds too.
You too?
But I can sleep well without them now.
How? Tell me your secret. I want to get better too--
Ms. Dam.
You told me once
that if you spill milk, you can wipe it up and dry the towel.
We get much more sunlight here than in Seoul,
so just stay here and relax instead of straining yourself.
I'm sure that's what your body wants the most.
Ms. Michelle wanted me to give you this.
She…
wants me to come back?
I was told it was the chairman's orders.
Did she tell you
to say that?
I'm only joking.
I must be drunk.
I should stop drinking.
I'll stop by the production plant then and head home afterwards.
Joong-hoon…
Because of me,
you've had to put up with a lot.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
What?
What is this?
DAM YE-JIN'S DAILY SCHEDULE
This is your daily schedule for the week.
Oh, come on.
I'm not some grade schooler on summer vacation.
You told me last night to relax and not strain myself.
You need to put in effort to rest well.
-I've tried all these before. -Doing them daily will be different.
But…
6:00 A.M. WAKE UP AND STRETCH 6:30 A.M. MORNING RUN
Go on ahead!
I need a breather.
Just for a bit…
COME ON NOW
Yes?
-Are you busy? -No.
Come out for a second.
I've been using a cervical pillow for a while,
and it helps me sleep really well.
Really?
Try it out.
Goodness.
Hey, it's nice.
I'll order one then.
What is all this?
They're so pretty.
The subtle scent of lavender will calm your mind
and help you fall asleep.
LAVENDER ICE CREAM
So they even sell lavender ice cream.
Thanks.
It's pretty good.
Let's go.
It's decaf!
It's hot.
I should have drunk it right away.
It's a frequency that helps with sleep.
What?
I'm so thirsty.
Geez, that startled me.
What's he doing at this hour?
What on earth?
Ouch.
That must hurt.
What on earth is he doing?
A saw?
Oh, my gosh.
He really is a strange person.
-Don't forget to breathe. -This is killing me.
-Ma'am! -Ms. Dam.
-Ma'am! -This way.
Ma'am! Ms. Yang…
Hang on. I'm going to throw up…
Changsik's living a much better life than I am.
Gosh, I'm aching everywhere.
I might fall asleep without the meds.
As if.
Life isn't that easy, Ye-jin.
You're still up?
I couldn't sleep, so I was reading.
It must be quite interesting.
Do you get very sentimental at night?
Have you not slept yet? Or did you wake up?
I'll go to bed soon.
Let me see that. Who knows? It might help.
You're not thinking
of using poetry as a sleeping pill, are you?
Well,
I can give it a try.
You seemed to have trouble sleeping well these days too.
No, I'm sleeping very well.
Really?
What's your favorite poem?
There aren't any marks in here.
I don't like scribbling in books.
Scribbling?
You're recording where you felt your emotions.
I was curious to see which lines spoke to you.
Try marking them.
I don't feel the need to mark anything.
Okay, fine.
I like the title of this.
"Light Sleep."
That year, we were each other's recklessness
We were the drowsiness that ate the same meals and faced each other
We were the resolution
That we'd do everything that other people did
We were tapping feet
Mouths that sang a song with no harmony
Hope that turned to face the still-fresh dawn
And a light sleep
That closed its eyes again, forgetting it had drifted off
I must be crazy!
Why did I fall asleep like that?
And when did I even fall asleep?
Goodness, I slept so well.
Nothing happened last night, right?
Have some breakfast.
Okay.
It's pretty hot, so be careful…
Isn't it hot?
I'm good with hot food.
There's a lab inspection today, so I'll be back pretty late.
"Pretty late"? How late is that?
I'll only know once I get there.
So you should have dinner on your own.
Okay.
I should do something.
What's with this guy?
Does he just clean all day or something?
Is there nothing to organize?
Everything's so neat and organized.
Wear your socks to bed.
He…
really is a strange person.
Did I wake you?
Mr. Mechoori.
What took you so long?
I told you I'd be home late.
Why were you sleeping here?
Did you take your meds?
You only took one pack, right?
Did you have dinner…
I missed you.
SOLD OUT ON YOU
What were you doing?
We were going to have breakfast.
Can I join you?
Everything he's doing for you is only because he feels responsible.
Reinstate Ms. Dam Ye-jin.
Ms. Michelle is not going to let this slide.
That's why I'm going alone.
Hey, Deokpung Village 1!
Today's the day we settle this. We're having a community festival.
This next game is charades.
Why aren't you guessing?
Hey, you fool!
Sit down. We have a lot to talk about.
Subtitle translation by: Juyoung Park